<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.oppokodibridge" name="OppoKodiBridge" version="2.0.9" provider-name="skull-01">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Browse in Kodi, play on your OPPO/M9205 over HTTP, switch the TV by CEC.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">OppoKodiBridge v2 is a clean-slate rewrite that supports exactly one chain: Kodi on a Ugoos AM6B+ (CoreELEC), an M9205 V1 OPPO clone as the player, and a TCL Q9L Pro as the TV. You browse and pick a file in Kodi; the add-on hands the file to the M9205 over its HTTP API and the OPPO plays it. Input switching is by HDMI-CEC: the OPPO asserts itself as the active source when it starts playing (One Touch Play) so the TV switches to it, and when playback ends Kodi reclaims the TV with CECActivateSource. All configuration lives here in Kodi — there is no companion Windows app. The OPPO HTTP API is community-reverse-engineered, not an official protocol, and this add-on is software-verified only — hardware validation is not claimed.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://github.com/skull-01/OppoKodiBridge</source>
    <news>v2.0.9 — INSTANT TV switching: instead of power-cycling the OPPO (~24s), the Kodi box now broadcasts a CEC &lt;Active Source&gt; for the OPPO's HDMI input (via cec-client) so the TCL switches immediately, OPPO undisturbed. Set the OPPO's HDMI physical address (default 1.0.0.0 = HDMI 1). v2.0.8 — Blu-ray disc folders (BDMV/VIDEO_TS) now play: the add-on mounts the disc folder's parent and plays the disc folder itself via /checkfolderhasBDMV (the OPPO won't play index.bdmv directly), with a STOP first to clear any stuck disc. Single files (MKV/ISO/m2ts) unchanged. v2.0.7 — TV auto-switch: the add-on now power-cycles the OPPO (#POF/#PON over :23) at the start of a handoff so CEC One-Touch-Play fires on power-on and the TV switches to the OPPO (verified the OPPO only asserts active source on power-on, not on play-while-already-on). Toggle: "Switch the TV to the OPPO on play". v2.0.6 — playback handoff VERIFIED working live on the M9205: wake via UDP NOTIFY OREMOTE LOGIN (:7624), init dance (firmware/setup/signin/globalinfo), login to the OPPO's own NFS server (from its device list), mount the file's folder, play /mnt/nfs1/&lt;file&gt;. Path mapping nfs://192.168.1.177/mnt/Super3/Super3Share to OPPO export srv/nfs/media. TV auto-switch (CEC) is the remaining piece. v2.0.5 — OPPO API rewritten to match the working M9205 protocol (loginNfsServer / mountNfsSharedFolder / appIconType signin / playnormalfile with /mnt/nfs1 + extraNetPath), server resolved from the OPPO's own device list, and socket timeouts no longer crash the handoff. This is the version that should actually play. v2.0.4 — playback monitor reads the OPPO's real /getglobalinfo flags (is_video_playing / is_audio_playing / is_bdmv_playing / is_disc_playing), confirmed on an M9205; fixes the TV being reclaimed mid-playback. v2.0.3 — packaging fix: the install zip now uses spec-correct forward-slash paths (the previous Compress-Archive build wrote backslashes that broke extraction on Linux/CoreELEC). No add-on code change. v2.0.2 — prefilled the OPPO IP (192.168.10.10) so the Ugoos/M9205/TCL chain is fully preconfigured out of the box; just install and play. v2.0.1 — URL-decode NFS/SMB paths so spaces and parentheses in filenames work; prefilled NFS path-mapping defaults. v2.0.0 — clean-slate v2. One chain only (Ugoos/CoreELEC + M9205 V1 + TCL Q9L Pro). Pure-HTTP handoff to the OPPO; CEC One Touch Play switches the TV; Kodi reclaims via CECActivateSource. All config in Kodi; no Windows configurator.</news>
  </extension>
</addon>
