<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.oppo203.iso.external" name="Oppo UDP-203 ISO External Player" version="2.9.10" provider-name="Perplexity Computer">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Version 2.9.10 Final: Software-verified release packaging.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Version 2.9.10 Final is the software-verified release packaging build after the Build 18 Full Release Gate regression/audit candidate. Version 2.9.10 Build 18 was the Full Release Gate regression, audit, and packaging candidate after Unified TV + AVR playback sequencing. This is a software-verified release; real hardware validation was not performed or claimed. It packages final v2.9.10 artifacts without adding new hardware features and preserves Build 17 unified TV + AVR playback sequencing behavior. It freezes the v2.9.10 software candidate, refreshes release evidence, confirms runtime ZIP cleanliness, and preserves all Build 17 sequencing behavior without adding new hardware features. Version 2.9.10 Build 17 safely hooks optional TV and AVR pre/post sequencing into the external-player flow. AVR sequencing runs only for eligible OPPO/external-player handoff, the AVR disabled path is a no-op, AVR and TV failures remain non-fatal, optional AVR restore runs only when enabled, existing TV restore continues to work, and startup power, service interception, playercorefactory.xml routing, NAS/AutoScript behavior, loose/raw file exclusion, runtime ZIP policy, the 99% coverage gate, and no-hardware-validation-claim posture remain preserved. Version 2.9.10 Build 16 adds AVR setup UI helpers, query-only AVR test actions, explicit user-action gates for power/input tests, sanitized AVR diagnostic export, and safety wording while leaving AVR disabled by default and not hooked into playback sequencing. Diagnostics sanitize credentials and state hardware_validation_claimed=false. Version 2.9.10 Build 15B adds a Sony AVR experimental request helper and Sony Audio Control API experimental request helper behind the disabled-by-default AVR framework. The skeleton adds Sony AVR preset metadata, explicit experimental acknowledgement gating, settings placeholders, validation helpers, sanitized diagnostics metadata, and tests. It uses guarded fakeable JSON POST helpers only after explicit acknowledgement, refuses Sony AVR execution unless experimental acknowledgement is enabled, never logs or exports Sony PSKs, passwords, credentials, tokens, or secrets, does not hook AVR into playback sequencing, and does not claim hardware validation. Version 2.9.10 Build 14 adds guarded Onkyo / Integra / Pioneer eISCP AVR driver support behind the disabled-by-default AVR framework. The driver uses TCP port 60128, ISCP frame magic, power-on payload !1PWR01, and input-select payloads !1SLIxx, builds valid eISCP frames, handles malformed response frames safely, returns non-fatal AvrResult objects on timeout, network, driver-error, and malformed-response paths, treats Pioneer as experimental/unverified, does not hook AVR into playback sequencing, and does not claim hardware validation. Version 2.9.10 Build 13 adds guarded Yamaha MusicCast / YXC AVR driver support behind the disabled-by-default AVR framework. The driver uses HTTP GET helpers for /YamahaExtendedControl/v1/main/setPower?power=on, /YamahaExtendedControl/v1/main/setInput?input=&lt;input&gt;, and /YamahaExtendedControl/v1/main/getStatus, parses JSON response_code, returns non-fatal AvrResult objects on non-zero response codes, invalid JSON, timeout, and network failure paths, does not hook AVR into playback sequencing, and does not claim hardware validation. Version 2.9.10 Build 12 Denon / Marantz AVR driver support remains preserved with PWON, SI&lt;input&gt;, PW?, and SI? helpers. Version 2.9.10 Build 11 AVR framework and settings skeleton remains preserved: AVR control, AVR power-off, and volume automation remain disabled by default. Version 2.9.10 Build 10 TV diagnostics, TV validation, and dry-run reporting remain preserved without launching ISO playback or contacting TV hardware during dry-run. Diagnostic exports sanitize SmartThings tokens, Sony PSKs, credentials, and command output, and always state hardware validation is not claimed. Version 2.9 release lineage remains preserved. Version 2.9.10 Build 8 polishes command/custom TV presets for LG webOS, Samsung command, Panasonic custom command, Vizio custom command, and generic custom command paths without adding risky native protocol expansion. Commands remain editable, {tv_ip} placeholder behavior is preserved, missing command values are represented as validation warnings, command failure remains non-fatal, and hardware validation is not claimed. Version 2.9.10 Build 7 adds the Roku TV ECP backend with local HTTP POST to /keypress/&lt;key&gt;, default port 8060, strict allowlisted input keys, editable Roku TV software presets, and non-fatal failure handling. Hardware validation is not claimed. SmartThings experimental guardrails from Build 9A/9B remain preserved. Version 2.9.10 Build 6 adds the Android / Google TV preset pack with editable ADB software presets for TCL, Sony, Hisense, Philips, Xiaomi, Sharp, Skyworth/Coocaa, Haier, and generic Android TV. No universal ADB HDMI command is claimed. Hardware validation is not claimed. Commands remain editable, ADB failure remains non-fatal, and the TV backend registry APIs from Build 5 are preserved. Version 2.9.10 Build 5 introduces a TV backend registry and software preset foundation while preserving existing public APIs switch_to_oppo(settings) and switch_to_kodi(settings), existing backend names adb, sony_bravia, lg_command, samsung_command, and custom_command, and existing non-fatal TV switching behavior. Version 2.9.10 Build 4 updates wizard/help/readiness wording for stock OPPO, Chinoppo-style clones, experimental clones, and OPPO-like successors. It explains that stock OPPO uses stock power behavior, clone-family models use clone-safe wake behavior with NAS/AutoScript readiness gates, and Reavon/Magnetar successors remain warning-only until hardware-proven. Version 2.9.10 Build 3 separates clone-safe capability gates from warning-only OPPO-like successor behavior. Chinoppo-style and experimental clone-family models remain eligible for clone-safe wake and NAS/AutoScript readiness gating, while Reavon and Magnetar UDP800/UDP900 remain warning-only unless real hardware validation proves compatibility. Version 2.9.10 Build 2 adds missing OPPO clone/successor model identifiers and safe aliases for M9200, M9205, CineUltra V203/V204, Magnetar UDP900, and M9702 V1/V2/V3 aliases while preserving Version 2.9.10 Build 1 unified hardware registry foundation. It does not change playback routing, OPPO command dispatch payloads, service interception, XML routing, NAS behavior, startup auto-power behavior, TV switching, AVR sequencing, or hardware-control behavior. Version 2.9.1 Build 16 i18n extraction legacy alias hardening remains preserved: tools/make_pot.py as a legacy compatibility alias while tools/i18n_extract.py remains the preferred facade for new automation. The legacy compatibility alias wording is preserved for Build 16 tests. It preserves Version 2.9.1 Build 15 Babel/gettext extraction tooling with tools/i18n_extract.py and babel.cfg, and preserves Version 2.9.1 Build 14 test naming/layout standardization with tools/test_layout.py and pytest markers for future version/build-specific tests, including the inherited flat tests/test_*.py transition policy. It preserves Version 2.9.1 Build 13 type hints and non-blocking mypy baseline, Version 2.9.1 Build 12 docs metadata/rendering pipeline with docs/sources.yaml and tools/render_docs.py, Version 2.9.1 Build 11 diagnostic logging fallback refactor, Version 2.9.1 Build 10 audit reporter refactor with typed audit checks and JSON reporter, Version 2.9.1 Build 9 settings schema and typed validation, Version 2.9.1 Build 8 settings exception narrowing, Version 2.9.1 Build 7 allowlist-driven packaging policy, Version 2.9.1 Build 6 local release automation scripts with scripts/verify.sh and scripts/package_release.sh, Version 2.9.1 Build 5 version single source of truth, Version 2.9.1 Build 4 dynamic audit evidence manifest discovery using release-evidence/*/MANIFEST.txt while preserving the legacy hard-coded evidence list fallback, Version 2.9.1 Build 3 externalized validated OPPO command map using resources/data/oppo_command_map.json and resources/lib/command_map.py, Version 2.9.1 Build 2 centralized disc classification and constants, and Version 2.9.1 Build 1 first-run Kodi startup auto-power wording clarity. No playback, OPPO command semantics, service interception policy, XML routing policy, NAS playback adapter, startup power implementation, settings runtime semantics, audit outcome semantics, packaging outcome semantics, TV switching non-fatal behavior, AVR sequencing, or OPPO hardware-control behavior changed during this build; only command/custom TV preset metadata, tests, and release evidence were updated in Build 8; only Roku TV ECP backend/preset metadata, key allowlisting, tests, and release evidence were updated in Build 7; only Android / Google TV preset metadata, tests, and release evidence were updated in Build 6; only TV registry/preset metadata, tests, and release evidence were updated in Build 5; Build 4 only updated player class wording/readiness guidance, tests, and metadata. Version 2.5.3 Build 1 precise 4K UHD disc-style service interception, Version 2.5.3 Build 2 conservative Option 4 XML routing, Version 2.5.3 Build 3 version identity reconciliation, Version 2.5.3 Build 4 playercorefactory.xml merge/rollback hardening, Version 2.5.3 Build 5 hardware-validation readiness export, and v2.5.3 Build 6 / Version 2.5.3 Build 6 pre-hardware release-candidate packaging freeze remain preserved. Hardware validation is intentionally not claimed until pending per-device tester results are provided. Preserved historical metadata: Version 2.5.0 Build 7 combined regression packaging candidate; v2.5.0 final package; Hardware validation is intentionally deferred. Version 2.5.2 Build 2 optimized runtime installable package policy remains preserved; Version 2.5.2 Build 3 deterministic Kodi-to-player path mapping helper; Version 2.5.2 Build 4 OPPO/Chinoppo NAS playback trigger adapter by family.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
    </extension>
</addon>
