<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.oppokodibridge.cec" name="CEC Control Experiment" version="0.4.5" provider-name="skull-01">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Experiment: no-blip OPPO playback with pure, spec-legitimate HDMI-CEC switching (no IR, no spoofing).</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">CEC Control Experiment is a fork of OppoKodiBridge v3 that keeps v3's playercorefactory handoff (Kodi routes disc content to an external OPPO player, so there is no pre-play "blip") but switches the TV using ONLY legitimate HDMI-CEC. The OPPO grabs its HDMI input via its OWN One-Touch-Play, forced by power-cycling the OPPO (it only asserts active source on a power-ON transition); Kodi reclaims its input by re-asserting its OWN active source. There is deliberately NO IR blaster and NO CEC injection / spoofed initiator (which corrupts the shared bus). The trade-off is the ~20-24s OPPO power-cycle on every handoff, accepted in exchange for zero extra hardware and a clean bus. Installs alongside v2 and v3 (different add-on id) for direct comparison. The OPPO HTTP API is community-reverse-engineered, not an official protocol.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://github.com/skull-01/CEC-Control-Experiment</source>
    <news>0.4.5 -- Fix the in-add-on Setup &amp; tests buttons (Ping / Control test / CEC switch-over). They all crashed before doing anything with "No valid addon id could be obtained" -- config.from_addon() called xbmcaddon.Addon() with no id, which Kodi can't resolve when a script is launched via RunScript (only the background service runs "in a normal Kodi manner"). Now passes the explicit addon id; the test fake was hardened to catch this class of bug.
0.4.4 -- Corrected the M9207 grab (hardware-tested live). The oppo_model setting now ONLY selects the NFS playback layout (M9205 = mount the file's folder + bare name; M9207 Plus / UDP-203 = mount the export ROOT + sub-path -- the part verified to work). The TV grab is the plain #POF -> #PON power-cycle for every model again: v0.4.3's #EJT-as-grab for the M9207 was WRONG -- on this clone #EJT ejects the disc tray and never grabs, and in fact NO network command can grab the TV (verified live: #POF is a sleep, #PON/#POW only ACK without powering on, and the unit fires CEC One-Touch-Play only on a full IR/remote power-on; the Kodi-side reclaim works fine). Removed the #EJT branch from power_cycle() + the desktop oppo_take_tv() and its now-pointless model selector. On the M9207 Plus switch the TV manually (or via an IR blaster) with grab_tv_on_play=false.
0.4.3 -- M9207 Plus / UDP-203 support (hardware-verified). The OPPO model setting's M9207 option now drives TWO clone-specific behaviours, confirmed live on an M9207 Plus (firmware reports UDP-203): (1) it grabs the TV with a single #EJT instead of the #POF->#PON power-cycle; (2) NFS playback mounts the export ROOT (path_to) and plays the full sub-path under /mnt/nfs1 -- e.g. mount srv/nfs/media -> play /mnt/nfs1/06pr0n/clip.mp4 -- the OPPOSITE of the M9205 model (mount the file's folder, play the bare name). handoff.play() is now model-aware; the default M9205 path is byte-for-byte unchanged. The M9207 file-play was verified end-to-end against real hardware (is_video_playing=True); the disc-folder case follows the same root-mount rule. This is why the add-on previously couldn't hand files to the UDP-203 -- its M9205-only mount-subfolder/bare-name shape was rejected every time.
0.4.2 -- OPPO model selection + an NFS doc/edge fix. New "OPPO model" setting (M9205 / M9207): the M9205 keeps the verified #POF -> #PON power-cycle to grab the TV; the M9207 clone uses a single #EJT instead (operator-reported for that clone -- on a genuine OPPO #EJT is the disc EJECT command, so this is hardware-validated by the operator, not by this code). Wired through the add-on (power_cycle), the in-app settings, and the desktop CEC Switcher (model dropdown); default M9205 = unchanged behaviour. Also corrected the PLAYING_DISCS_FROM_NETWORK guide's checkfolderhasBDMV example (it double-included the mounted folder; the code's /mnt/nfs1/&lt;disc folder&gt; form was already right) and fixed play_bdmv so a disc structure sitting at the export root sends the bare /mnt/nfs1 instead of a dangling /mnt/nfs1/. 82 off-box tests.
0.4.1 -- Second hardening sweep. A multi-agent adversarial hunt found 9 more real bugs (all in error / edge paths); all fixed + pinned by regression tests (78 total). Highlights: the HTTP stop-watcher now uses a tri-state playback probe so a transient network blip is never mistaken for a stop (no premature mid-playback TV reclaim) and is bounded by read-failure + watch-time ceilings so it can never hang and skip the reclaim; serial control maps every failure (missing termios, termios.error, bad baud, absent POSIX flags) to a non-fatal OppoError; #PON still fires when #POF fails; the guided CEC switch-over test is no longer blocked for serial-control users (and Ping reports the serial cable, not a misleading :23 UNREACHABLE); the desktop CEC Switcher surfaces save failures instead of losing settings silently, and treats a connect-then-reset OPPO as reachable.
0.4.0 -- Bug-fix sweep. An adversarial hunt found 13 real bugs, all in previously-untested branches; all fixed + pinned by regression tests (63 total). Highlights: disc-folder mapping for share-root / trailing-slash / .iso-under-BDMV; HTTP status vocabulary (unknown/no-disc tokens now read idle, so the monitor can't loop forever and miss the reclaim); a dropped :23 socket now raises OppoError instead of a raw OSError (so the reclaim and the HTTP fallback aren't skipped); writer/reader profile-path mismatch (both now masterprofile); playercorefactory.xml backup/remove is marker-guarded (never clobbers a user's own file); XML-escaped paths; serial settings wired into the UI; from_addon honours dataclass defaults for undeclared ids; .cec log tag.
0.3.0 -- Clean modular rebuild: detector / handoff / cec / monitor / orchestrator (single-responsibility). The CEC reclaim now goes straight from the orchestrator to Kodi via JSON-RPC -&gt; script.cecreclaim -&gt; CECActivateSource (no flag, no stale-flag class of bug), still single-shot and never re-asserting. New Settings -&gt; Setup &amp; tests: Ping OPPO, Control test (#QPW), and a guided CEC switch-over test. (0.2.0: explicit single-shot reclaim. 0.1.0: fork of v3, IR removed.)</news>
  </extension>
</addon>
